Have you ever gotten an urgent call
from a family member
saying they're in trouble
and need money right away?
Here's something scary: scammers can
now clone someone's voice
using just a few seconds of audio
from social media.
They call you pretending to be
your child or grandchild —
saying they're in an accident
or arrested and need money now.
So what do you do?
The answer is simple:
hang up and call them back.
Call them on the number you already
have saved in your contacts —
not the number that just called you.
Your real contact.
You can also set up a family code word —
something only your family would know.
Agree to use it in any emergency.
If they don't know it — hang up.
The three red flags to remember:
extreme urgency,
requests for gift cards
or wire transfers,
and asking you to keep it secret
from other family members.
Hang up, call them back on your
real number, set up a code word.
This one habit stops AI voice scams
every single time.
For more free guides in plain English,
visit TekSure.com.
[END]