That amazing deal might be a
fake website. Here's how to check.
Every time you shop online,
start with this quick check.
Look at the top of your browser
at the website address.
You should see a padlock icon
and the address starts with https.
No padlock? Leave immediately.
Don't enter any details.
Second — check the website name
very carefully.
Scammers make sites like
"amazon-deals.net" that look real.
The real Amazon is just
amazon.com. Nothing extra.
Third — the prices. If
everything is 70-80% off —
with no explanation,
the site is probably fake.
Check the payment options.
Real stores take credit cards.
If a site only takes gift cards
or bank transfers — leave.
Those methods have no
consumer protection.
When you do shop online,
use a credit card if you have one.
Credit cards give you the
strongest protection of all.
If something goes wrong, your
card company must refund you.
If a purchase goes wrong,
contact the seller first.
Give them 5 days. No response?
Open a dispute through the platform.
Check the padlock, read the address,
and always pay by card.
Full guide at TekSure.com.