Is a stranger looking at your
Facebook photos right now?
They might be. Here's how to
stop that in five minutes.
Open Facebook on your phone.
Tap your profile photo.
Tap Settings and Privacy,
then tap Settings.
Scroll down and tap
Audience and Visibility.
Tap Posts. Change who can see
your posts to Friends only.
Now tap Profile Information.
Find your friends list setting.
Set it to Only Me. This stops
scammers targeting your friends.
Go back. Find "How people
find and contact you."
Set your email and phone number
lookup to Friends only.
That's your Facebook
locked down. Now Instagram.
Tap your profile photo.
Tap the three lines top right.
Tap Settings and Privacy,
then Account Privacy.
Switch on Private Account.
Only approved followers see you.
One more thing — if you get
a request from a "friend" —
check your friends list first.
Scammers clone real profiles.
They use real photos to trick
the people who know you.
You've protected your privacy
on two platforms in five minutes.
For the full guide
with screenshots —
visit TekSure.com.