If you ever get a call saying
your computer has a virus —
hang up. Here's what's really going on.
This is a tech support scam —
one of the most common ways
people lose money online.
The truth: Microsoft, Apple, and Google
will NEVER call you
out of the blue to say
your computer has a problem. Never.
What about scary pop-ups?
If a website says
"YOUR COMPUTER IS INFECTED —
CALL THIS NUMBER" — that's fake.
Real virus warnings come from
your antivirus software,
not from a website.
To close a fake pop-up:
press Alt + F4 on Windows,
or Command + Q on a Mac.
Scammers want three things:
remote access to your computer,
your credit card number,
and your personal information.
If you already let someone in:
disconnect from the internet now.
Turn off your WiFi,
then run a full security scan.
Change your passwords from
a different device.
Call your bank if you shared
any payment information.
No real company will ever call you
about a virus.
If someone does — hang up.
Never give them access.
For plain-English guides,
visit TekSure.com.
[END]